(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T05:27:04.858713",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
え、みなちゃま！
Hey everyone!
本日はツルギ初めて単体2026 ライヴ・イン・モーションに、お越しくださいまして、
Today, for Tsurugi's very first solo 2026 Live in Motion, thank you for coming,
まことに、ありがとうございます！
thank you truly!
開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the start, we have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください。
This stream contains some recorded parts, but also live parts, so please comment a lot to hype it up!
今もね、今日わあって、いっぱい、お、こんにちは！きちゃ！パチパチと、ありがとうございます。
Even now, saying hi a bunch... yay, hello! Oh, you're here! Clapping, thank you.
え、みなちゃま！
Hey everyone!
本日はツルギ初めて単体2026 ライヴ・イン・モーションに、お越しくださいまして、
Today, for Tsurugi's very first solo 2026 Live in Motion, thank you for coming,
まことに、ありがとうございます！パート2！
thank you so much! Part 2!
キチャ！ 大丈夫ちょ、パート2！
It's here! It's alright, part two!
キチャ！ ありがとう！
It's here! Thank you!
ええ、配信のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ届け初め生誕祭2026です。
Um, the stream hashtag is #TodokeHajimeSeitansai2026.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post a lot on SNS.
ええ、凱旋中は、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。
Photo shooting with cameras or smartphones is very welcome.
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです。
We'd be happy if you posted a lot and hyped it up.
じゃあそれでは、起こすまで、おまちばらく... お待ちください！
Well then, until we wake you up... please wait!
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to a useless life,
くどからないよ 紛い物だってば ラリアッチュ
I won't ramble on, it's a fake, rariatchu!
偶然息してるようなもの 不条理浴びながら僕は home
Just barely breathing, bathing in absurdity, I'm home.
才はゼロ どうにかしちまっ ちゃって るけど
My talent is zero, even though things are all messed up,
歓声は no だってば 虚 愛にもたれた言葉で 心拍数
The cheers are a 'no', empty heart rate fueled by leaning on love.
生きてく程 胸は沈んでいく どうなってんだろ うな？
The more I live, the more my chest sinks. How will it turn out?
この音が揺れるの かいつまんでもしょうがねえ
This sound wavers, no use summarizing it.
汗かき稼ぐお金は どんだけ？ ああどうこうだ
How much money do I earn sweating? Ah, this and that.
そんなもんか 五月雨乞い和な
Is that all? A rainy wish prayer.
バンザイ 無能な命に から回ってく 脳を満たしてくれ
Banzai, to a useless life, fill my spinning, overactive brain.
未来予想図なんかない くどからないよ 紛い物だってば それ
There's no future projection, I won't ramble, it's a fake.
半端者ならやらない nutty tune 朱色になって僕は 思い通り
A nutty tune a half-assed person wouldn't do, turning crimson, I have it my way.
太陽系で蹲った 罵詈雑言インベーダー
Crouching in the solar system, abusive invaders,
足が止まっているシュガーゲーザー のらりくらり躱すわ
Sugar gazers with stopped feet, dodging lazily.
初めましてカミサマ もし救われるのなら 腹切るわ 今から
Nice to meet you, God, if I'm to be saved, I'll commit seppuku right now.
get down 揺らり動かす
Get down, moving swaying.
get down 飲み込んだ清濁 君を狂わせてんだ
Get down, the clarity and turbidity you swallowed are driving you mad.
めっけたもんじゃおどろかかねえ 汗かき生きた 最期 もあってけねえ
Won't be surprised by what's found, can't even have a final moment.
なんだかんだ そんなもんさ 虚しいわな
This and that, it's just like that, how empty.
バンザイ 無能な命に から回ってく 脳を満たしてくれ
Banzai, to a useless life, fill my spinning brain.
未来予想図なんかない くどからないよ 紛い物だってば それ
There's no future projection, I won't ramble, it's a fake.
半端者ならやらない nutty tune 朱色になって僕は 思い通り
A nutty tune a half-assed person wouldn't do, turning crimson, I have it my way.
絵の具で 絡まってくのさ
Entangled in paint,
満たしてくれ 未来をずっと
fill my future forever.
輪郭 なんか描けない
I can't even draw an outline,
くだらない馬鹿 居残りだってそれ
it's just a worthless detention anyway.
半端者なら やれない毎日を
Days that half-hearted people can't handle,
若い狼だって 野暮は甘いぜ
even young wolves are naive if they're unrefined.
パララ ここはきっと奈落だ
Parara, this is surely the abyss.
声にもならぬ声が
A voice that cannot become a voice
腹の底からせりあがるんだ
wells up from the bottom of my stomach.
「ダメ！それ！」押し殺す本能
"No! Not that!"—suppressing instinct.
ユラユラ瑠璃色の海から
From the swaying lazuli sea,
幽霊車と雲ヶ島
a ghost train and Kumogashima.
ただただ君は呟くんだ
You simply murmur,
「人は怖いね」と
"People are scary."
今弾ける七色
Now the seven colors burst forth.
アイアイ アイアイ 穹を舞って踊り散らすのさ
Aye-aye, aye-aye, dancing and scattering across the sky.
ファッションビートで気取って
Putting on airs with a fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
don't act like a cheap madman.
報われない悲しみ食らい尽くそう
Let's devour all unrewarded sorrow.
ファッションビートに染まって
Soaked in the fashion beat,
言うことない なら息しても
if you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イアイア 笑え少年よ
is useless. Aye-yah, aye-ah-yah, smile, young boy!
「ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
"Isn't it great? Isn't it great?
この先は何もわかりんし
We have no idea what lies ahead.
無礼じゃないか 無礼じゃないか」
Isn't it rude? Isn't it rude?"
クソッタレ 見てられん煩悩
Damn it, these worldly desires are hard to watch.
呻呼 荒れ狂う 世の中だから
Groaning, because the world is running wild,
アイアイ アイアイ 穹を舞って終わりにするのさ
aye-aye, aye-aye, dancing across the sky to make an end of it.
ファッションビートで気取って
Putting on airs with a fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
don't act like a cheap madman.
報われない悲しみ食らい尽くそう
Let's devour all unrewarded sorrow.
ファッションビートに染まって
Soaked in the fashion beat,
言うことない なら息しても
if you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イアイア 笑え少年よ
is useless. Aye-yah, aye-ah-yah, smile, young boy!
絵に描いたようなストーリー
A story painted like a picture,
僕の性を塗れぬほどに落ちぶれた
fallen so low I can't even paint my own nature.
モノクロに過ぎる日を
Days that pass by in monochrome—
乗り越えられたら
if we can overcome them,
呻呼 今夜は笑って
groaning, tonight let's smile,
あの幽霊車にキスをして
kiss that ghost train,
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
and be reborn in seven colors.
ファッションビートで気取って
Putting on airs with a fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
don't act like a cheap madman.
報われない悲しみ食らい尽くそう
Let's devour all unrewarded sorrow.
ファッションビートに染まって
Soaked in the fashion beat,
言うことない なら息しても
if you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イアイア 笑え少年よ
is useless. Aye-yah, aye-ah-yah, smile, young boy!
絵に描いたようなストーリー
A story painted like a picture,
僕の性を塗れぬほどに落ちぶれた
fallen so low I can't even paint my own nature.
モノクロに過ぎる日を
Days that pass by in monochrome—
乗り越えられたら
if we can overcome them,
呻呼 今夜は笑って
groaning, tonight let's smile,
あの幽霊車にキスをして
kiss that ghost train,
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
and be reborn in seven colors.
ファッションビートで気取って
Putting on airs with a fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
don't act like a cheap madman.
報われない悲しみ食らい尽くそう
Let's devour all unrewarded sorrow.
ファッションビートに染まって
Soaked in the fashion beat,
言うことない なら息しても
if you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イアイア 笑え少年よ
is useless. Aye-yah, aye-ah-yah, smile, young boy!
ファッションビートに染まって
Soaked in the fashion beat,
言うことない なら息しても
if you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イアイア 笑え少年よ
is useless. Aye-yah, aye-ah-yah, smile, young boy!
はあ、楽しー！
Haah, that was fun!
たのしー！
So fun!
やっぱ歌って踊るの楽しい！
Singing and dancing is really the best!
いや、さっき ちょっとぶっ壊れちゃったにしけろ
Man, I kind of broke down a bit earlier...
え、なんかダンスとかやってたにしか
Eh, like, what was I doing with the dancing?
え、なんか撮ってました？ え、なんか撮ってましたよね？
Wait, was that being recorded? Wait, it was, right?
え、てかこれ配信して これ配信されてます？これ
Wait, is this streaming? Is this being streamed right now?
え？ ちょ ちょさっきんとこあるんですけど初めにも
Huh? Wait, there's that part from the very beginning too—
なんかコメントちょ、すげえ流れてるんですけど。
Like, the comments are scrolling by super fast.
反転してて読めまちぇん！
They're mirrored so I can't read 'em!
ええと、なんかパチパチって、拍手してくれてって
Um, like, pat-pat, clapping for me, and
なんか、かっこよチューギって、なにや？
like, what's this "cool chugi"?
ええと、すごいなんか、え？え、くしゃ？くしゃ？なんか、くしゃ早いしゃれだ。
Um, wow, like... Eh? Eh, sneeze? Sneeze? Like, sneezing so fast.
ええ、なんかありがとうございますよ。
Um, like, thank you so much.
はじゅタグ、初配信始めて、10時26分で、なんかたくさんポチッと、してくれてるみたいなですけど。
The #HajimeTag, since the first stream started at 10:26, it looks like a lot of you are clicking and doing it.
なんだろ、このタグは。わかんないけど、初め祝ってもらってるし、ポチッとしてもらったら嬉しいかも。
What's this tag? I don't get it, but you're celebrating Hajime and if you tap it, I might be happy.
ありがとうまっちょ。はじゅ初めて歌ったり踊ったりとか、素人の私で
Thank you so much. As an amateur like Hajime singing and dancing for the first time...
本当はこう、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに憧れて、ちょうど状況したいなとか思ってるんですけど、ちょっと勇気がなくて。
Actually, I've always admired performing in front of lots of people, and I thought about moving to Tokyo and stuff, but I just don't have the courage.
え？
Eh?
はじめなら大丈夫？いける？
Hajime, you'll be fine? You can do it?
え、コメントの方、ちょっとどう思っとる？
Um, what do you guys in the chat think?
かわいい、なんて。
"So cute," what...
あ、ダンスうま？すごい褒められてる！
Ah, "good at dancing"? I'm getting praised so much!
あ、かっこいい！あ、褒められてる！やった！
Ah, "cool"! Ah, I'm being praised! Yay!
じゃあみなさんに、すごい勇気をもらったので、はじめ
So, you guys gave me a lot of courage, so Hajime...
行ってきます！夢を目指して、状況してくる！
...is going! Aiming for my dream, I'm going to Tokyo!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を 二人はひとりきり さらり
In the season of storms, two made it by oneself, easily
明け行く夕日の中を 今夜も昼下がり さらり
In the dawning sunset, at night in the early afternoon, casually
どれほど朽ち果てようとも 最後にゃ笑いたい
No matter how bad our bodies decay, we’d love to laugh at the end of time
何のために戦おうとも 動機は愛がいい
No matter what you’re fighting for, I want you to be motivated by love
新しい日々は探さずとも 常に ここに
No need to look for brand-new days, they’re always here with us
色々見てきたけれど この瞳は永遠に きらり
Though I’ve seen a lot of things in my life, my eyes will always and forever be sparkling
あれほど生きてきたけれど 全ては夢みたい
Though I’ve lived that long, everything I’ve been through is like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも 私は君がいい
Everything looks attractive, but you’re the only one for me
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where have you been? I’ve been looking for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me there, take me there
何もかも 捨ててくよ
Giving up everything, and I’ll go with you
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, to everywhere
荒れ狂う 季節の中も 群衆の中も
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
君とならば さらり さらり
With you, I can go smoothly, smoothly
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
Our brand-new future, embarrassing past, everything will be shiny, yeah
無くしてしまったものを 振り返って ほろり
Thinking back on what I had to lose, it makes me weep
時には途方に暮れて ただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
Sometimes I’m all at sea, just swaying in the wind, unsteadily
息せき切ってきたの
I came running out of breath
行き先は決めたの
Decided where to go
迷わず行きたいけど 保証はしないよ
I’d rather not get lost but who knows?
何か分かったようで
I thought I knew something
何も分かってなくて
In fact I knew nothing
だけどそれが分かって 本当に良かった
But at least I know it and I’m so glad
新しい日々は探さずとも 常に ここに 常にここに ここに
No need to look for brand-new days, they’re always here, right here
色々見てきたけれど この瞳は永遠に きらり
Though I’ve seen a lot of things in my life, my eyes will always and forever be sparkling
あれほど生きてきたけれど 全ては夢みたい
Though I’ve lived that long, everything I’ve been through is like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも 私は君がいい
Everything looks attractive, but still, you’re the only one for me
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where have you been? I’ve been looking for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me there, take me there
何もかも 捨ててくよ
Giving up everything and I’ll go with you
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, to everywhere
荒れ狂う 季節の中も 群衆の中も
In extreme weather, in a crazy crowd
君とならば さらり さらり
With you, I can go smoothly, smoothly
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
Our brand-new future, our embarrassing past, everything will be shiny, yeah
荒れ狂う季節の中を二人手を取り合って さらり
In the raging season, two people holding hands, smoothly
明け行く夕日の中を今夜も昼下がり さらり
In the dawning sunset, tonight once again in the early afternoon, smoothly
どれほど朽ち果てようとも最後にゃ笑いたい
No matter how much we decay, I want to laugh at the very end
何のために戦おうとも動機は愛がいい
No matter what we fight for, I want the motive to be love
新しい日々は探さずとも常にここに
New days are always right here without searching
色々見てきたけれどもこの瞳は永遠に きらり
I've seen many things, but these eyes sparkle forever
あれほど生きてきたけれども全ては夢みたい
Though I've lived so much, everything is like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも私は君がいい
Everything has its charm, but you're the one I want
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where were you? I was looking for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me there, take me there
何もかも 捨ててくよ
I'll throw everything away
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, to everywhere
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where were you? I was looking for you
連れてって 連れてって
Take me there, take me there
何もかも 捨ててくよ どこまでも
I'll throw everything away, to anywhere
どこまでも どこまでも
To anywhere, to everywhere
荒れ狂う 傷の中も 群衆の中も
In the raging wounds, in the crowd
君とならば さらり さらり
With you, smoothly, smoothly
新しい日々も 拙い過去も
New days, clumsy past
全てがきらり
Everything is sparkling
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
幕開けの合図が いつか来る back
The cue for the curtain rise will come back someday
sit up 姿勢正して ひねくれた態度じゃ不合格です
sit up, straighten your posture, a twisted attitude is a fail
不幸中の幸いは飽きてしまうわ
The silver lining gets boring
get up 目を覚まして いい加減な言いなりに黙ってうなずいてちゃ no no no 伸び代がないわ
get up, wake up, if you just nod silently to sloppy orders, no no no, there's no room to grow
i got 123456 things on my mind 思考一向にまとまらない what do i do
i got 123456 things on my mind, my thoughts won't come together at all, what do i do
running i'm running away 追いかける yesterday 決める覚悟 迷いは捨て 'cause it's gonna hurt more the longer you wait
running i'm running away, chasing yesterday, make up your mind, throw away hesitation
駆け引きなんていらない say whatcha wanna say 憂鬱なマンデー 気分はブルース 痛みを噛んで削ぎ落す 古びた bandage いらない do whatcha wanna do
no need for games, say whatcha wanna say, gloomy Monday, blues in the mood, biting through the pain and scraping it off, I don't need a worn-out bandage
man up 気付けないね 言い訳ばかり conversation もう勘弁
man up, you can't notice? Conversations full of excuses are already enough
つまずく恐れちゃ どこもいけないわ stand up 世は罪だらけ 歯を見せれば見せられる nightmare? 無感情になれるなら 教えて頂戴
if you're afraid of stumbling, you can't go anywhere, stand up, the world is full of sins, showing your teeth means being shown a nightmare? If you can become emotionless, teach me please
tell me abcdefg 正解のライン 言葉選び出せない what do i do
tell me abcdefg, the correct line, I can't choose my words, what do i do
finding i'm finding a way 追いかける one more day 決める覚悟 迷いは捨て 'cause it's gonna hurt more the longer you wait
finding i'm finding a way, chasing one more day, make up your mind, throw away hesitation
駆け引きなんていらない say whatcha wanna say 憂鬱なマンデー 気分はブルース 痛みを噛んで削ぎ落す 古びた bandage いらない do whatcha wanna do
no need for games, say whatcha wanna say, gloomy Monday, blues in the mood, biting through the pain and scraping it off, I don't need a worn-out bandage
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
幕開けの合図が いつか来る back
The cue for the curtain rise will come back someday
波瀾万丈な人生 like がちょうどいいのさ 君が作る show time を見せて見せてちょうだい
A dramatic life like this is just right, show me the show time you create
過ぎ去っていく day by day 考えたって don't look back さあ highway
passing day by day, no matter how much you think, don't look back, now highway
いつだってそう 身を任して let's ride away
Always like that, surrender yourself, let's ride away
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
幕開けの合図が いつか来る back
The cue for the curtain rise will come back someday
春夏秋冬じゅーとに やりやれ everybody grab your hands
Spring, summer, autumn, winter, all year round, everybody grab your hands
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合う可能性は変人間
Rushing in at the very last second, the possibility of making it in time is abnormal
気持ちはゴロゴロされども脳労 現実はずっと甘くないね
My feelings roll around, but brain-fatigued, reality isn't that sweet
働きアリ日本人に everybody grab your hands
Working ant Japanese, everybody grab your hands
お決まりのすてんだい how can it be my safe of mind
The usual stage, how can it be my safe of mind
誰もこれも色のない世界に興味ない
No one is interested in a world without colors
見るのここが 笑える場所 got to find your way
Look, this is a place where you can smile, got to find your way
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
幕開けの合図が いつか来る back
The cue for the curtain rise will come back someday
波瀾万丈な人生 like がちょうどいいのさ 君が作る show time を見せて見せてちょうだい
A dramatic life like this is just right, show me the show time you create
過ぎ去っていく day by day 考えたって don't look back さあ highway
passing day by day, no matter how much you think, don't look back, now highway
いつだってそう 身を任して let's ride away
Always like that, surrender yourself, let's ride away
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
波瀾万丈な人生 like がちょうどいいのさ 君が作る show time を見せて見せてちょうだい
A dramatic life like this is just right, show me the show time you create
過ぎ去っていく day by day 考えたって don't look back さあ highway
passing day by day, no matter how much you think, don't look back, now highway
いつだってそう 身を任して let's ride away
Always like that, surrender yourself, let's ride away
Welcome to our theater ほらおいでよ
Welcome to our theater, come on over
幕開けの合図が いつか来る back
The cue for the curtain rise will come back someday
波瀾万丈な人生 like がちょうどいいのさ 君が作る show time を見せて見せてちょうだい
A dramatic life like this is just right, show me the show time you create
過ぎ去っていく day by day 考えたって don't look back さあ highway
passing day by day, no matter how much you think, don't look back, now highway
いつだってそう 身を任して let's ride away
Always like that, surrender yourself, let's ride away
飛びっきり show time 慣れても show time
An extraordinary show time, even if you're used to it, show time
あなたの show time を見せてちょうだい
Show me your show time
飛びっきり show time 慣れても show time
An extraordinary show time, even if you're used to it, show time
あなたの show time を見せてちょうだい
Show me your show time
え、
Eh?
あんにょん！
Annyeong!
星川、まじツイッチ配信じゃんよ！
Hoshikawa, this is seriously a Twitch stream!
ご存知かしら、ありがと！
Did you know? Thank you!
え、あん、なんか、超偶然でちゃったけど
Uh, um, somehow it just happened by total coincidence
の日の誕生日ってことで、色々語り合おう。
It's your birthday, so let's talk about you.
私もしたかったわ。
I wanted that too!
何をしたかったの?
What did you want to talk about?
まあ、嬉しかったわ。ありがとう。
Well, I'm glad we could do this. Thank you!
え、でもでも、あの...
Wait, why...
このシアターって、勝手に入っていいんですか?
How did you get into this theater anyway?
まあ...
Well...
ダメかもしれないわ。
maybe you shouldn't have.
ダメなの?
D-Dame na no?
うん。
Yeah.
え?じゃあ怒られるぞ、ここで。
Eh? Then we're gonna get scolded!
まあ、怒られるわ。
Well, you're gonna get scolded.
なんでここに連れてきてくれたんですか?
Why did you bring me here, then?!
あそこの人がもう準備してるわ、こうやって。
That person over there is already getting ready, look.
怖い、怖い!
Scary, scary!
え、そんな!ぶっしょな、違います。
What, really? This is serious!
あの、この人...
Wait, this person...
オーディション、出場じゃおしゃれ!
If you pass the audition, you'll look cool, right?
オーディション受かる、出場さ、こうにしよう。
You're gonna pass the audition!
ってこと?
For real?!
そうそうそう。ここでオーディションやってるんだ。
That's right, so we're doing the audition here.
そうだよ。受けた方がいいんじゃない?ね。
That's right. You should take it, right?
立たないと受からない。
If you don't, you won't pass.
受かるよ、受かるよ。
You'll pass!
怖い、怖いよ。
Scary, scary!
受かるよ、ね。
You'll pass, hey!
あれ、星街すいせいじゃない!?
Hey, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei!?
おい、行けねえ!
Oh, get out of here!
じゃあね!
See ya!
ちょ、ちょ、待って!えー!
Wait, wait, wait! Hey!
あれや。
Are ya?
え?
Eh?
どっちや。
Which one?
あ。
Ah.
へえ。
Hey.
ステップはお静かに
Step lightly,
作詞:Lily Mizusaki
Lyrics: Lily Mizusaki
作曲:mARUTA mANABU
Music: mARUTA mANABU
Set like a visitor in a party, party chain
抜け出し 慈しむ 荒い様 劇場
stepping lightly, just as you please, all the way to heaven.
Step past the boundary 教えるわ
Step past the boundary of what you're taught,
転がるの 重くも無ない この世界で
rolling right along in your own sweet way.
強気の決まり隠しして
A bold and sudden change of heart,
少しずつ笑って
smiling a little bit more each day.
上向き盛り 上り気質 慎重 ちょっと極彩色
A definitive, soaring, elegant performance,
しずめてあげるわ
stepping up close to lift you up!
Set like 同じダンサー ばかり冗談めいて
Set like the same old dancer, just playing a game,
Spilla アイムお一人の自分に勝つの
spilling out all my thoughts, winning on my own.
だって盗まれたら
Even if I get stolen away,
取り返すのがこうたう
turning it back around is all I can do.
アイズ 二人で 慎重にアシスト
Stepping close together, matching our stride,
ひらりとかわして眠るの目
gliding right past, avoiding your gaze.
さらりと言葉は調子合わせジャン
With hands held light and nonchalant,
からに無言 一撃
just one bold, striking gesture!
慎重にちょっと極彩色 鎮めてあげるわ
Stepping up close to make you a star,
Set like a visitor in a party, party chain
抜け出し 慈しむ 荒い様 劇場
stepping lightly, just as you please, all the way to heaven.
Step past the step and I そのまま踊れよ
Step past the boundary, just as you are,
踏み出して見せろよ
stepping out boldly to seize the stage.
そこで決めるの
Deciding it right here and now,
誰も奪いはしないわ
whatever anyone else might say,
胸に秘めてる法則と
I've got the rules locked deep in my heart.
静かに踊って、静かに踊ってよ
Let's dance softly, dance softly!
全部押し込んで
We'll push it all the way.
BAD HATTER
作詞:中路もとみ
Lyrics: Nakaji Motomi
作曲:DYES IWASAKI
Music: DYES IWASAKI
sweetie night に mary jane
Sweetie night and Mary Jane,
かかと カンカン tap する 伽藍堂
tapping with the heels to the rhythm of the mob.
secret sign ほら ご招待
A secret sign, look, your invitation.
ちょっとしゃれた帽子と
With a stylish hat and
説教でナビゲート
a lecture, I'll navigate you.
すっぴん最後のルナティック
The last lunatic without makeup,
すでに今宵主演したいトゥーグラビーズ
already wanting to star tonight...
坂道走ってパレード
Run up the slope, parade,
今はこの欲望に踊れや
now dance to this desire!
言うなら夜が明ける前まで
If I must say, until dawn breaks,
愛はいつくすべき
love should be cherished.
You have bad hater
支配なるモンスター
ruling monster.
We are bad hater
目覚めろ最強ムナーセス
awaken, strongest "Munasesu"!
バムバムムーンライト 厨二のダンスフロア
Bam bam moonlight, chuunibyou dance floor.
We have stakeholder 競争にのまれ踊れ
Get swallowed by the rivalry and dance!
劣情サントラ
Passionate soundtrack,
何空中飛び交うキンキンドール
floating in mid-air, golden dolls.
回想ないなら平等さ
If there's no flashback, it's equality;
今は若きも私語り合う
now even the young talk to each other.
すっぴん最後のルナティック
The last lunatic without makeup,
照れ隠しがみ打ちクラジトーク
shy concealment and whisper-like talk.
一緒にどうです？お嬢さん
How about together, young lady?
雪降らしと新しき者がシャワータイム
Snow falling and newcomers' shower time!
夕立とかどんな見た目だろうが
No matter what kind of sudden shower it looks like,
気にする暇もない
there's no time to care!
You have bad hater
支配なるモンスター
ruling monster.
We are bad hater
目覚めろ最強ムナーセス
awaken, strongest "Munasesu"!
バムバムムーンライト 厨二のダンスフロア
Bam bam moonlight, chuunibyou dance floor.
We have stakeholder 競争にのまれ踊れ
Get swallowed by the rivalry and dance!
Wubba lubba dub dub...
You have bad hater
支配なるモンスター
ruling monster.
We are bad hater
目覚めろ最強ムナーセス
awaken, strongest "Munasesu"!
バムバムムーンライト 厨二のダンスフロア
Bam bam moonlight, chuunibyou dance floor.
We have stakeholder 競争にのまれ踊れ
Get swallowed by the rivalry and dance!
うわ、待てさっきのやつ、なにもっちゃうの？
Woah, wait, what's that guy holding?
は？バッチュ！
Ha? A cross!
ばっ、ばっちュってどういうこと
Wh- what do you mean a cross?
お前な、持ち替えして、お嬢さんのしざいだったの？
Hey, you, swapping it, was it the young lady's property?
今日だってさっき、なんかノリノリで、きゅぶきゅぶじゅどぅるるってやってたじゃん！
Today, just a moment ago, you were grooving along saying "kyubu kyubu judururu"!
あ、出てけやった！なんだよ、お前も頑張って
Ah, get out! What, you work hard too,
一応さ、てっちしてさ、ねえ！
at least make an effort, hey!
なんかさ、だ、だってさ、動けないんだけど！
I mean, b- but, I can't move!
いや、なんか話したけっても、駄目みたいだ。
Even if I want to talk, it seems no good.
なんだよ、こっから願い下げだ！こんな、こんなちまった！ててってやろう！
What, I'm done with this from here! Let's do tetete!
no thank you , alright ?
No thank you, alright?
能天気どうかしして（して）いる
How is the airheadedness doing?
「不適切」「指摘」には低姿勢で
Low profile against "inappropriate" and "criticism",
正義し放し mr. x 放火している
justice unleashed, Mr. X is committing arson.
「※真偽不明」なんて正気じゃない
"※ authenticity unknown", that's not sane.
夜は on and on and on
The night is on and on and on.
僕ら怨念飲んでへべれけじゃん
We drink our grudges and get dead drunk, right?
目には？歯には？簡単だ吸って吐いてジャッジメント
Eyes? Teeth? It's simple, inhale, exhale, judgement.
ようやく今宵無礼講決行です
Finally, tonight we carry out unreserved liberty.
皆様ナンセンス甚だナンセンス
Everyone, nonsense, hugely nonsense!
イキるな勿れ黙れ黙れ
Don't act cool, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス誠に遺憾です
This world is nonsense, truly regrettable.
お気の毒ね哀れ哀れ仕方ないね
Too bad, pathetic, pathetic, can't be helped.
ほら精々気張っていっていらっしゃい
Come on, do your best and go on.
じゃあ閻魔によろしく言っといて
Well, say hello to Enma for me.
be quiet , alright ?
Be quiet, alright?
拡声器セールしている
Loudspeakers are on sale.
「名義不明だとしてもまいどあり」
"Even if the name is unknown, thank you for your continued patronage."
夜にカーテンコールを
Give a curtain call to the night,
まさに宣言通り dirty party night
exactly as declared, dirty party night.
右も左も断頭台降りて湧いたチェックメイト
Checkmate emerging from the scaffold on both right and left.
ようやく今宵無礼講決行です
Finally, tonight we carry out unreserved liberty.
皆様ナンセンス甚だナンセンス
Everyone, nonsense, hugely nonsense!
イキるな勿れ黙れ黙れ
Don't act cool, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス誠に遺憾です
This world is nonsense, truly regrettable.
お気の毒ね哀れ哀れ can't you understand ?
Too bad, pathetic, pathetic, can't you understand?
「もう、駄目」って諦めた件 何回繰り返さすの? 馬鹿なの?
"Give up already," you said. How many times must we repeat this? Are you stupid?
負け惜しみの会話 狂ってしまって 描いた良心
A sore loser's conversation, driving me mad, drawing a conscience.
「もう、無理」って去ろうとした採点
"It's impossible now," the grading trying to walk away.
罪悪戯じゃ済まないね
It won't end with mere mischief.
不備スペアは余った
The defective spares were left over.
売る手口は投げて邁進
Throwing away sales tactics, pressing forward.
「じゃ、またね」
"Well, see you later."
扇状街路を壊して澱んで行く
Smashing the fan-shaped streets as they grow stagnant.
明日も未来も何もなくなってしまえばいい
Tomorrow and the future, I wish it all disappeared.
ああ、まだボクの人生は未完成なのに
Ah, even though my life is still incomplete—
――最初から終わっていた。
——it was over from the start.
「運命」なんて知りたくない!
I don't want to know about "destiny"!
「もう、駄目」って諦めた件 何回繰り返さすの? 馬鹿なの?
"Give up already," you said. How many times must we repeat this? Are you stupid?
扇状街路を壊して澱んで行く
Smashing the fan-shaped streets as they grow stagnant.
この世は「駄目」鼻から「駄目」
This world is "hopeless," "hopeless" from the start.
霧の中で 「ダメレ」「ダメレ」
In the mist, "damere," "damere."
この世は「駄目」本当に「駄目」
This world is "hopeless," truly "hopeless."
昨日の毒ね 「アマルレ」「アマルレ」
Yesterday's poison, "amalure," "amalure."
現状アンダースタンド 「ダメレ」「ダメレ」
Current understanding, "damere," "damere."
ほら、せいぜい気まずいって笑えさ
See? At least laugh it off awkwardly.
SOSピースでごめん不遜
Sorry for my arrogance with SOS pieces.
代償ライセン青く澄む夕暮れ
A price license in the clear blue twilight.
おっ、どこ行くの? あぶなっ!
Hey, where are you going? Watch out!
危ないじゃないですか、はっ? 何言ってんのさ
Isn't that dangerous? Huh? What are you saying?
お前、短足こ?
Hey, are you short-legged?
え? 段差ですけど?
Huh? These are steps, you know?
私もう、段差で!
Whoa, me too, because of the steps!
え, なんか凄い段差がいっぱい出てきた!
Whoa, so many weird steps showed up!
え、ちょっと待って、なんか初めて聞いた段差のオーディション落ちちゃってさ…
Wait a minute, I failed the audition for that first-ever step...
もしかしてあそこの階段ですか?
Could that be the stairs over there?
え、それ私も落ちました!
Eh, I failed that too!
え、私もち! 私も私も! みんな落ちた仲間!
Eh, me too! Me too, me too! We're all failed comrades!
あのミニバン調心サイン選手ネオンな
Hey, that mini-van top-notch sign-in idol neon—
おい、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃねえか!
Hey, let's show them properly!
おおーっ! もう壁とは踊らないぞ!
Alriiiight! No more dancing with walls!
一生祈るよな!
Pray for your life!
3メートルのハキ、水みやすぅ! 歯押すに落ちる、はかすべる!
A 3-meter hockey broom sweeping water, falling into chaos, falling apart!
宇宙一の番長になる、届き始め!
Becoming the universe's number one bancho, starting to reach it!
弱っち、うちらの始まりは、ここから!
Weaklings, our beginning starts right here!
Hey, boy 平凡に born in the ニッポン
Hey, boy, ordinarily born in Nippon,
産声オゲー 行き先は荒野
A baby's first cry, heading into the wasteland.
ノーマル以下が何処にして地下深く眠る鉱脈掘れますか？ 知るか！
Can anything below normal dig up veins sleeping deep underground? Who knows!
のるかそるかしかねえこの世の中 確かな価値観など無価値か
Win or lose in this world, are solid values worthless?
カッと立ったってこの葛藤で生まれたtakeはcutできんよ
Standing up fiercely, the takes born from this struggle can't be cut.
I can't be someone else, oh I know, I know... このブレイクを壊したいの 死にたいの?
I can't be someone else, oh I know, I know... Do I want to break this break? Do I want to die?
間違っている未来でも俺には光ってる
Even in a mistaken future, it shines for me.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊し どうしようもないままが自分なんだ
Burn this fighting spirit, smash those iron bars, being hopeless is just who I am,
こっから始まった
it starts right here.
いつかの童心持って 努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
Keeping our childhood heart, working hard, we should be able to fall in love with our dreams.
こっから、こっから始まった
It starts right here, right here!
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通りいってないだけで 予定通りローリングローリング転がってけ
1, 2, 3, 4, just not going in order, roll and tumble as planned.
よりどりみどり 緑の一生 1, 2, 3, 4 順番通りいってないだけで 予定通りローリングローリング転がってけよ こっから始まった
A life of endless choices. 1, 2, 3, 4, roll and tumble as planned, yo! It starts right here!
こっから どこから 分からないだって 燃料すらもすっからかん
From here, from where? I don't even know, my fuel is completely empty.
こりゃアカんわ 楽観し 簡単には済まない まさに難関
This is bad, optimism won't make it easy, truly a difficult barrier.
一人になりたくても人だらけ さらけ出すにも一苦労なわけ
Even if I want to be alone, it's full of people, exposing myself is a struggle.
聞きたくないサイレンピーポー だけどどこ行ったって "ピーポーピーポーピーポー"
Sirens I don't want to hear, but wherever I go, "peepoh peepoh peepoh".
黄信号でずっと進行 辛抱した先は歩こうぜレッドカーペット
Advancing through yellow lights, let's walk the red carpet after enduring.
たりりりりだった come on!
It was tally-lilly-lilly, come on!
よりどりみどりってさっき言ったろ? 明日ありと思う心の仇桜
Didn't I just say "choice of many"? Cherry blossoms blooming with the thought of tomorrow.
生きてることが青天の霹靂 しかし悔しさで黒く燃える腹中
Living is a bolt from the blue, yet my gut burns black with frustration.
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊し どうしようもないままが自分なんだ こっから始まった
Burn this fighting spirit, smash those iron bars, being hopeless is just who I am, it starts right here.
いつかの童心持って 努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ こっから始まった
Keeping our childhood heart, working hard, we should be able to fall in love with our dreams. It starts right here.
こっから、こっから始まった
It starts right here, right here!
Hey, boy
平凡に born in the ニッポン
Ordinary, born in Japan,
産声オギャー 行く先は荒野
First cry, destination is a wasteland.
ノーマル以下が 如何にして
How can anyone below normal
地下深く 眠る 鉱脈 掘れますか？
mine the ore sleeping deep underground?
知るか！ のるかそるか
Who knows! Sink or swim,
しか ない この 世の中
that's the only way in this world.
確か な 価値観 など 無価値か
Are certain values worthless?
カッとなって転がる通り
Losing my temper, rolling down the street,
生まれたてから 圧倒的
overwhelming ever since I was born.
I can be so one way, so I know I know
このブレーキを 壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I really do.
これだけじゃやれねえってわかってる
I know I can't do this with just this,
でもこれしかねえから これにかかっている
but this is all I've got, so it rides on this.
間違っている未来でも 俺には光っている
Even in a wrong future, it shines for me.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子ぶち壊し
Burning this fighting spirit, smashing those iron bars,
どうしようもないままが自分なんだ
being helpless is just who I am.
こっから始まるんだ
It all starts right here.
いつかの童心 持っていただろうし
Maybe I had some childhood innocence,
夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
and I should be able to fall in love with my dreams.
こっから こっから 始まるんだ
It starts right here, right here.
Yo! 1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り
Yo! 1, 2, 3, 4, right in order,
言ってないだけで予定通り
just as planned, even if unsaid.
Rollin' rollin' 転がってけ
Rollin' rollin', keep rolling on,
よりどりみどりの一生
a life of endless choices.
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り
1, 2, 3, 4, right in order,
言ってないだけで予定通り
just as planned, even if unsaid.
Rollin' rollin' 転がってけ
Rollin' rollin', keep rolling on.
Yo! こっから始まるんだ
Yo! It starts right here.
Ayy こっから どっから わかんない
Ayy, I don't know where to start from here,
だって燃料自体は すっからかん
'cause my fuel tank is completely empty.
こら かかんわ 楽観視 簡単には済まぬ まさに難関
Can't take it lightly, it's a real challenge.
一人になりたくても人だらけ さらけ出すにも一苦労なわけ
Even wanting to be alone, it's crowded with people.
聞かれたくない surrounding people
Surrounding people I don't want to hear me.
でもここに立って みろよ people people
But try standing right here, people, people!
俺悪くない 何も間違ってない 自分じゃない
I'm not at fault, nothing's wrong, it's not me.
何かのせいにしたい 天才じゃないのっせ分かんないな
I want to blame something, I'm no genius, who knows.
これフィクションじゃない 読みなさい
This isn't fiction, read it carefully.
天賦の才などない でもやめられないみたい
I have no natural talent, but I can't seem to stop.
あいつらほうが馬鹿みたい
Those guys look like fools.
見てみたい こっから燃える未来
I want to see a future burning from here.
メラメラ まだまだ 自分で決めつけんな
Burning bright, don't limit yourself yet.
限界探せ お前の視点変え
Find your limits, change your perspective.
ホントの自分なんて いやねえよ
There's no true self like that.
高くなくちゃダメ 低くてもダメ
Can't be too high, can't be too low either.
と思い込んでることこそが
That very assumption itself
好きこそ物の上手なれ
is what passion makes you master.
次こそ吠えろ根比べ
Next time, bark it out in a war of attrition.
I can be so one way, so I know I know
このブレーキを 壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I really do.
Ah 四の五の言わずに動け
Ah, move without making excuses.
道なき道ほど進める
The roadless road is the one we can advance on.
どの誹謗も嫉妬なら燃料
Any slander or jealousy is just fuel.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子ぶち壊し
Burning this fighting spirit, smashing those iron bars,
どうしようもないままが自分なんだ
being helpless is just who I am.
こっから始まるんだ
It all starts right here.
数年後 - a few years later -
- A few years later -
I can't see what's behind those eyes
Just wait, talk a little before they're right
誰かの理想像に
To someone's ideal image,
耳を傾けてしまったのさ
I ended up lending an ear.
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion.
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな
dance like you've gone mad.
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
何かを言おうとして
Trying to say something,
間違探しタースタート合図
the starting signal of fault-finding.
Why's everybody's eyes on me
慣れてしまうものね 視線の的
You get used to being the center of attention.
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感じるプレッシャーは押し殺してさ
Suppressing the pressure I feel,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
いい子気取りじゃ no no no
no acting like a good girl, no no no.
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな
Dance like you've gone mad.
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
"So show me what you got"
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな
Dance like you've gone mad.
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
"So show me what you got"
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな
Dance like you've gone mad.
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
"So show me what you got"
I can't take it back no more
I guess it's too late to call it off
感情のない世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion,
Tell me who I'm supposed to be
I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな
Dance like you've gone mad.
"Said you wanna be a superstar"
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher
ラララ...
La la la...
はぁ、みんな、ありがとう！
Haah, everyone, thank you!
仲間と励まし合って、みんなから勇気をもらって
Encouraging each other with my friends, getting courage from everyone,
こうしてステージに立って、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることができました！
and being able to perform in front of so many people on this stage!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
そしてなんと、Xトレンド1位、ありがとうございます！
And what's more, number one on X trends, thank you!
そしてチャンネル登録者さまも120万人さまにいたみたいで、本当にありがとうございます！
And it looks like we've reached 1.2 million subscribers as well, thank you so much!
わあ、嬉しい！
Wow, I'm so happy!
こうしてね、こう夢を追いかけて、上京して、
Like this, chasing my dream, coming to Tokyo,
こうたくさんの人の支えになって、ステージに立ってたくさんの方の前でパフォーマンスすることができました！初EP『Gotcha!』リリース決定、わあ！
and with the support of so many people, being able to perform on stage! My 1st EP "Gotcha!" is decided, wow!
まあでもね、この物語を綴っていって、たくさんの素敵な1つ一つの楽曲をお借りして、あの作る事ができたので、本当にありがとうございます！
Well, but woven into this story, borrowing each and every wonderful song to create this, thank you truly!
初めも、曲をたくさん作れるようにがんばります！
I'll do my best to create lots of songs too!
そして、えっとこれが最初の100万人記念の新衣装になります！衣装の名前は『不埒踊道1号』です。市原たつつやさんに仕立てていただきました！
And, um, this is the new outfit to commemorate 1 million subscribers! The name is "Buraku Ododa Ichigo". It was tailored by Tatsuya Ichihara!
みなちゃんがね、応援してくれたおかげです！ありがとうございます！で、今回の新衣装ね、
It's thanks to everyone supporting me! Thank you! And for this new outfit,
髪がロング！そして、あそこがなんかすごく長く見えるデザインで、あざぁ、テクティアなおみやっち。じゃあぜ、みなちゃんなんかおかしくない？
hair is long! And, that part looks super long in design, ah, textie na omi-yacchi. Everyone, isn't something weird?
曲腹が、ない！うちょだ！ちょんなばかな！ちょんなばかな！曲腹がないだちょん！
Belly is gone! No way! That's impossible! That's impossible! My belly is gone!
うわあ、うちょです！ぴょこぴょこもあります！うわあ！ま、ぴょこぴょこないと、脳みそ出ちゃうからね、必要だよね。
Wow, no way! There are pyoko-pyoko too! Wow! Well, without pyoko-pyoko, my brain would pop out, so it's necessary.
で、あと、ジャケットも脱げます！おや？この後この後の面会で紹介するので、気になる方、画面に来てください！
And also, the jacket can come off! Oh? I'll introduce it in the next meeting, so if you're curious, come to the screen!
え、続いてなんと、新曲を初披露しようと思います！みなちゃん、盛り上がる準備、できてますか？こーー！うぇーーい！どんご可愛い！ありがとう！
Um, next, what's more, I'm thinking of premiering a new song! Everyone, are you ready to get hyped? Go! Uei! Dongo is cute! Thank you!
とってもね、かっこよくて、なんかテクティいな感じの曲になっているので、ぜひ聴いてください！それでは、いきます！ディープダイブ！
It's very cool, and kind of a tekty style song, so please listen to it! Well then, here we go! Deep Dive!
late night 今夜は with my girlies
late night tonight with my girlies
baby すぐ出なよ (let's get party , yeah )
baby hurry up and come out (let's get party, yeah)
頭から つま先 キメ て る lips
lips styled from head to toe
okay , ma ladies i need you to show me
okay, ma ladies I need you to show me
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
wow seriously gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
scream , scream , scream and shout ay
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
wow seriously gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
scream , scream , scream and shout ay
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
me and my girls , me and my girls 見て よ
me and my girls, me and my girls look
we 're amazing , we are so amazing
we're amazing, we are so amazing
me and my girls , me and my girls ここから
me and my girls, me and my girls from here
dive
yes , i 'm a hot queen
yes, I'm a hot queen
dive , let 's deep dive , i wanna deep dive
dive, let's deep dive, i wanna deep dive
dive , yeah deep dive , ay , ay , ay
dive, ya deep dive, ay, ay, ay
dive , let 's deep dive , i wanna deep dive
dive, let's deep dive, i wanna deep dive
dive , yeah deep dive , yeah , yeah , yeah
dive, ya deep dive, yeah, yeah, yeah
let 's get out of control
let's get out of control
girl
you like it like that
まじ you 're so hot
seriously you're so hot
burn
まさに queen
truly a queen
hot queen hot queen
ワンストローク で star , glow
star, glow in one stroke
bare minimum でも hard core
hard core even with bare minimum
ネイル 光 って so shiny
nails glowing so shiny
マスカラ し て i 'm burning
applying mascara, i'm burning
髪 down ? それとも pony ?
hair down? or pony?
ooh - la - la ooh - la - la
ooh-la-la ooh-la-la
視線 を control
control your gaze
i don't mind them
誰か の approval
anyone's approval
i don't need it at all
wow マジ gorgeous , thanks you look so badass
wow seriously gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
scream , scream , scream and shout ay
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
wow マジ gorgeous , thanks you look so badass
wow seriously gorgeous, thanks you look so badass
scream , scream , scream and shout
scream, scream, scream and shout
夜に映し出す思い出眺めて
Looking at the memories projected in the night
日身体中鳴り響いた鼓動
The heartbeat that echoed through my body that day
さよならなんて言いたくなくて i always fight my darkness
I didn't want to say goodbye, i always fight my darkness
i’m trying to hold your hand again
i’m screaming, "no!" in my head
'cause we just weren't meant to be
we’re just back to where we were
that’s okay
we weren’t meant for each other
もう君のいない この街で
In this city without you anymore
まだ君を探す 私がいて
There is still me searching for you
you know that i have to let you go
it’s all for the best
'cause we just weren't meant to be
仰向けになって星空眺めた
Lying on my back, looking up at the starry sky
あの日何気なく見つめていた その笑顔に
That smile you looked at so casually that day
思えば全部 君色に染まって 忘れられなくて
Thinking about it, everything was dyed in your color, I couldn't forget
i’m trying to hold your hand again
i’m screaming, "no!" in my head
'cause we just weren't meant to be
we’re just back to where we were
that’s okay
we weren’t meant for each other
もう君のいない この街で
In this city without you anymore
まだ君を探す 私がいて
There is still me searching for you
you know that i have to let you go
it’s all for the best
'cause we just weren't meant to be
i wish i was the one
spending the rest of my life by your side
it’s hard to think that i’m not
'cause i love you, i love you
but we just weren't meant to be
we’re just back to where we were
that’s okay
we weren’t meant for each other
もう君のいない この街で
In this city without you anymore
まだ君を探す 私がいて
There is still me searching for you
you know that i have to let you go
it’s all for the best
'cause we just weren't meant to be
はい、てことで
So, with that said...
生誕グッズのご予約が開始します！
Starting goods reservations begin!
では、夜木はじめ 生誕記念2026のグッズセットはこんな感じです！
Here is the information for the Yadorigi Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026!
一つずつご紹介します！
I will introduce them one by one.
一つ目は、ぷんぷんぱんちょアクリルスタンド！
First is the "Bun Bun Buncho Acrylic Stand."
二つとも机などに引っかけることができて、イラストは88はじめに変えていただきました！
Both versions of Pancho can be hung on desks and the like, and I was able to change the illustrations to match 8/8 Hajime!
怒っているのがポイントです！
The angry expression is the main point!
二つ目は、はじめとおそろいチョーカー！
Second is the "Hajime Matching Choker."
はじめのシンチョーとおそろいのチョーカーです。うちのチャームが可愛い！
This is an exact match with Hajime's actual choker design. The little charm is so cute!
首のサイズが本ラインよっていう方は、他のバンなどに付けてください！
If you want it to be your actual size, please attach it to a choker or something similar.
三つ目は、BANCHOジャージ！
Third is the "BANCHO Jersey."
裏面のイラストはおもちチャウダーちゃんに変えていただきました！おもてめは刺繍になってます。ババル先輩のキジがとてもよかったので、同じのにしていただきました！
The illustrations on the front and back were done by Omochi Chowder-chan! The back is embroidered, and since Baruchan-senpai's jersey was so nice, I made one just like it!
最後、ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ブラックオーロラ衣装ver.！
Lastly, the "Plushie Keyholder Black Aurora Ver."
初めて出した人気のぬいぐるみの新バージョンです！あの時買えなかったよっていう方、ぜひお迎えしてくだチャイ！
This is a new version of the popular plushie from before! If you weren't able to get one back then, please pick one up!
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And the Full Set bonus is right here!
今回のライブのチケット風カードを、全員にじっくりデザインに描かせていただきます！
These are ticket-style cards with a printed autograph, and you'll get them for buying the full set!
去年のねライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで、今年もっとに力を入れることができました！
Thanks to everyone buying so many goods at last year's live, I was able to put even more effort into this one!
ありがとうございます！わん今回のライブも楽しんでいただけますと！
Thank you so much! I hope you all enjoy this live as well.
きれいなグッズもお迎えしていただけると今後の励みになります！
I would really appreciate your support by getting the goods as well!
よろしくおねがいします！以上グッズ紹介でした！
That concludes the goods introduction!
あーしみなった！
Ah, it's about time...
このあとラストのパート、一緒に盛り上がっていってください気持ちよ！
Let's all get fired up for the rest of the live together, everyone!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
それでは今回はライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います。
Now, I'd like to introduce everyone who helped out with this live.
まずはダンサー！
First up, the dancers!
夢芽にゃん！
Yumenyan!
そして、潮音りあ！
And Shion Ria!
うみみや！
Umimiya!
空！
Sora!
ありがとう。そして、この場にはいないんですけど、振り付けの……みゆき先生！
Thank you. And though they aren't here, our choreographer... Miyuki-sensei!
たっぷの、あやか先生！
Tappu's Ayaka-sensei!
で、ぽっぴ、とど先生！
And Poppi's Todo-sensei!
だんつ、かんつ、ゆか先生！
Dantsu Kantsu's Yuka-sensei!
ぽーかどかんつ、まりあ先生！
Pokeru Kantsu's Maria-sensei!
そしてゲストの豪華出演の皆様！
And our gorgeous guest performers!
こちまじ、ついぜんちゃん！
Kochimaji's Tsuizen-chan!
箱すべーるずちゃん！
Hakosuberuzu-chan!
いざきりおなちゃん！
Izaki Riona-chan!
じょじみやづちゃん！
Jojimiyazu-chan!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so very much!
そして、今見えない中で稼働してくださってるスタッフの皆さん、そして初めての目の前にいてくれてる、見てくれてた皆さま、本当にありがとうございました！
And to the staff working behind the scenes, and everyone watching right before our eyes, thank you so much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います。改めてタイトルは『Deep Dive』！
Now, I'd like to introduce my new song in detail. Once again, the title is "Deep Dive"!
はい、MV公開、この配信のすぐあとです！
Yes, the MV drops right after this stream!
音源リリースは本日24時からです！
The audio releases tonight at midnight!
皆さんたくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
I hope you'll listen to it a lot!
じゃあ、それではここで重大発表いきたいと思います！こちらの動画をご覧ください！
Well then, time for a major announcement! Please take a look at this video!
コラボ決定!!
[Collaboration Confirmed!!]
COMING SOON!!
わあ！すごーい！この度、はじめとFILAちゃんのコラボが決定しちゃいましたー！
Wow, amazing! A collaboration between Hajime and FILA has been decided!
わあ、嬉しいー！ありがとうございます！
Yay, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そしてなんと、チュニックを含むアパレルをプロデュースさせていただきました！
And what's more, I got to produce apparel including a tunic!
やったー！初めてっぽいカジュアル感をね、
Yay! Giving it a casual feel for the first time,
取り入れながら男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインしていただきました！
while designing it to look great on both men and women!
一着一着はじめのこだわりを詰め込んだチュニックにしていくので、直近を楽しみにしていてください！
Each piece is packed with my personal touches, so please look forward to it!
で、そして今回なんと、あのチュニックだけじゃなくてね、ジャージとTシャツとあ、キャップもプロデュースしちゃった！さらにコラボにあたって、オリジナルのコラボロゴをFILAちゃんと作りましたー！どうどーん！
And this time, not only tunics, but jerseys, T-shirts, and caps too! We also created an original logo with FILA! Ta-da!
わあ、かわいい！実はこのね、ロゴFILAちゃんと一緒に打ち合わせをしてあの、考えましたはじめ。
Aw, cute! Actually, I thought of this logo after having a meeting with FILA.
あ、こうこういう感じでね、実際にこう手書きをしながら打ち合わせをして、どの色がいいかなっていろんな色見を出してもらって作りました。
Like this, sketching ideas during meetings and checking various color samples to find the best one.
ま、一目でね、こうはじめだってわかるこうミニばんちょうのシルエットがいいかなと思って入れてみました。
I thought a Mini Bancho silhouette would make it instantly recognizable as Hajime, so I added it.
え、このロゴがね、コラボの商品にもつきます！楽しみにしててねー！
This logo will also be on the collaboration merchandise! Look forward to it!
で、実はね、アパレル以外にもFILAちゃんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、皆さんの詳細な情報が出るの、ぜひお楽しみに待っていてください！
Also, other collaboration items besides apparel will be released, so please stay tuned for more details!
で、このあとにですね、メンゲンでアンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし、
And after this, there's a member-limited encore live starting at 21:15,
で、この新曲についても色々詳しく見ていければと思いますので、
and I'd like to look into this new song in detail as well,
ぜひまだの方はチャンネル登録と通知ようにして、メンゲンもはじめてのすぐのライブとアンコールライブも一緒に楽しめてハッピーだなと思います！
so please subscribe and turn on notifications so we can enjoy the live and encore live together!
え、お別れを知ると、新曲MVこのあとすぐ公開、21時からグッズ販売、21時15分からアンコールライブ、24時新曲音源リリースです！
To recap: new MV dropping right after, goods on sale at 21:00, encore live at 21:15, and audio release at 24:00!
ありがちょねー！
Thank you so much!
それではメンゲンアンコールライブでお会いしましょー！
See you at the member-limited encore live!
バイバーイ！いっぱいコメントありがちょ！また近かった！
Bye-bye! Thank you so much for all the comments! See you soon!
あはっ、ありがとっ！
Ah, thank you!
直す網…！いつもぱぁめと楽しいを共有してくれてありがとう！
Naosoumu...! Thank you always for sharing the fun with Paame!
あなたがチームが期待してくれるともっと頑張りたい！
Knowing you and the team have expectations makes me want to work harder!
もっと成長したいって思えるよ！
It makes me want to grow even more!
はじめての形を形にしてくれてありがとう♡
Thank you for giving shape to this first form♡
これからも直す網にとってかっこいい存在でいたいです！
I want to continue being a cool presence for Naosoumu!